http://www.idahosteelheads.com/en/terms-of-service

Skip to content
TERMS OF SERVICE
ECHL Inc. and ECHL Properties, LLC (collectively, “ECHL,”“we,”“our,”“us”) respect your privacy and value your trust and confidence. This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) applies to our websites, mobile applications, online shop and other online and mobile services that link to or post this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Services”), and explains how we collect, use, and disclose information through the Services. By using the Services, you agree that you have read and understood the terms of this Privacy Policy and agree to the terms hereinPlease note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the individual ECHLMember Teams(the “Member Teams”). Further, we may direct you to a site that is operated by a third-party service provider and a different privacy policy may govern the information collection by thethird-party service provider.Information CollectionYou generally are not required to actively provide information about yourself when you visit the Services, but we may collect certain information automatically. When you register with our Services, sign up for contests or sweepstakes, participate in surveys, access various content or features, submit comments or content, use a send-to-a-friend feature, post on social media sites (including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram) or directly contact us with questions or feedback, we may ask you for the following types of information:how to contact you; demographic information, likeyour gender and your age; financial information, like credit card or other payment information; real-time geolocation information (where you are); how you would like for us to contact you; search requests you have made; and additional information as otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.You may choose not to provide this information, but it may limit our ability to provide some of the Services.We may collect certain information automatically when you visit the Services, including: your Internet Protocol (IP) address, which is the number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet and that can sometimes be used to derive your general geographic area; your device type or mobile carrier; other unique identifiers, including mobile device identification numbers and advertising identifiers (e.g., IDFA); your browser type and operating system; sites you visited before and after visiting the Services; pages you view and links you click on within the Services; information collected through cookies, web beacons (Web beacons are small pieces of code placed on Web pages, videos, and in emails that can communicate information about your browser and device to a server. Beacons can be used, among other things, to count the users who visit a Web page or read an email, or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a user viewing a Web page or email.), Local Shared Objects (sometimes called “Flash cookies,” which are similar to cookies in that they are stored on your device and can be used to maintain information about your activities and preferences), and other technologies; information about your interactions with e-mail messages, like the links clicked on and whether the messages were received, opened, or forwarded; andStandard Server Log Information.Use of InformationWe may use information that we collect through the Services for a variety of purposes, including to: provide you with, maintain, or administer the Services, the products, promotions, services, newsletters, and information you request; respond to your correspondence to us; contact you via email and otherwise about your account or contest submission; conduct behavioral analysis to better serve you with offers and content that is of interest to you;perform business analyses, or for other internal purposes to improve the quality of our business, the Services, and other products and services we offer; publish stories, comments, photos, and other information posted in our interactive online features; customize and personalize your use of the Services, including providing you with tailored advertising; and as otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.With your separate consent, we may contact you via email and otherwise about products, services, contests, and events that we think might be of interest to you, and otherwise send you promotional material or special offers on our behalf or on behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties.Sharing of InformationLimited members of the ECHLmarketing and IT departments, as well as the third-party vendor that processes fan data on behalf of the ECHL, ECHL.TV, and other associated ECHL products may access and otherwise process personal information in connection with their job responsibilities or contractual obligations.We may share your information with service providers that perform certain functions or services on our behalf. We may share information with third-parties, like social networking platforms, so that they may send tailored communications on our behalf via their platforms. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.We may share your information with our subsidiaries and affiliates as they exist from time to time.We may share your information with Member Teamswhere you have indicated a preference, each of whom has its own privacy policy, which is available on the Member Team’srespective website.Please read their respective privacy policies for more information.With your prior permission, we may share your information with select business partners so that they can provide you with special offers, promotional materials, and other materials that may be of interest to you. If you do not elect to have your information shared, it will not be shared with such third parties. We take measures to help ensure that our partners protect the confidentiality, integrity, and security of any information we share with them. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners.Please read their respective privacy policies for more information.In some cases, a third-party may operate or host a contest or sweepstakes on the Services and collect your information. In those cases, we urge you to review the third-party’s privacy policy for that contest or sweepstakes before participating. We take measures to help ensure that our partners protect the confidentiality, integrity, and security of any information we share with them. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners. Please read their respective privacy policies for more information.We may use third-parties to advertise on the Services. These third parties may set their own cookies or similar web technologies to collect information about users’ online activities over time and across different websites. Please read their respective privacy policies for more information.To manage your preferences, you may opt out here: http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/.If our assets are transferred in any manner, we may transfer your information as part of such transaction.We may disclose your information to third parties in order to protect the legal rights, safety, and security of the ECHL, our affiliates, subsidiaries, business partners, and the users of our Services, whether or not legally required.We may share information with third parties when you post information to a user profile or a public area of the Services. If you post to these interactive features, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. We cannot ensure that parties who have access to such information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when using these features.We may share information with third parties when you consent to such sharing.We may share aggregate information, like demographics and usage statistics, with third parties.We may share your geolocation information with service providers that perform certain functions or services on our behalf. These companies are authorized to use precise geolocation information only as necessary to provide these services to us. We also may share your geolocation information with third parties so that they may provide you with geographically relevant advertising. If you wish to stop the further collection of your geolocation information, whether collected through location services, Bluetooth, or microphone access technology, please opt-out using your device settings.Cookies and Similar TechnologiesThe Services use technologies like cookies, beacons, tags, pixels and scripts. By using the Services, you consent to our use of cookies and similar technologies.You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, butif you reject cookies, your ability to use certain features of the Services may be limited.The Services may use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here: https://helpx.adobe.com/flash-player/kb/disable-local-shared-objects-flash.html.We may use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Services. This software may record information like how often you use an application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and from where an application was downloaded.AdvertisingWe partner with third-party advertisers to serve and display advertising on the Services. These partners may use cookies and Web beacons to collect information about your activities across different websites and services to provide you with relevant advertising. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here: http://optout.aboutads.info/. To serve and display advertising relevant to your location, the Services may also track your device’s precise geolocation by responding to beacons or inaudible signals sent to your device’s microphone. If you do not want the location of your device to be tracked by the Services, please opt-out using your device settings.Social NetworkingThe ECHL has worked with certain third-party social media providers to offer you their social networking services through our Services. These social networking services may be able to collect information about you, including your activity on our Services. These third-party social networking services also may notify your friends, both on our Services and on the social networking services themselves, that you are a user of our Services or about your use of our Services, in accordance with applicable law and their own privacy policies. If you choose to access or make use of third-party social networking services, we may receive information about you that you have made available to those social networking services, including information about your contacts on those social networking services. Your interactions with those social networking services are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the relevant service.You also may be able to link an account from a social networking service (e.g., Facebook, Google+, Yahoo!) to an account through our Services. This may allow you to use your credentials from the other site or service to sign in to certain features on our Services. If you link your account from a third-party site or service, we may collect information from those third-party accounts, and any information that we collect will be governed by this Privacy Policy.Links to Other WebsitesThe Services may contain links to other websites or online services that are operated and maintained by third parties and that are not under our control or maintained by us. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by us of those other websites, the content displayed therein, or the persons or entities associated therewith. This Privacy Policy does not apply to this third-party content. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third-party websites or services.Data Security and Data IntegrityWe have security procedures to help protect your information. When you enter sensitive information (like a credit card number), we, or our third-party vendors, encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). However, no data transmission or storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to the Services and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your information.Data RetentionWe will retain your information only for as long as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.Children’s PrivacyThe Services do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information from children under the age of 13. If we are made aware we have collected personal information from a child under 13 years old in a manner that is inconsistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), we will delete this information as soon as possible.Communications Preferences and AccessYou may choose to receive communications from us. You may opt out of receiving commercial emails from us by clicking on the opt-out or “unsubscribe” link included in the commercial e-mails you receive. Please note that opt-out requests may take some time to be effective. Your opt-out request will not apply to messages that you request or that are not commercial in nature.If your information changes, or if you no longer desire to use the Services, you may request that we update or remove certain information by signing into your account and making the required changes, by emailing our Customer Support at echl@echl.com, or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will make reasonable efforts to respond to your request within 30 days.You may opt-out of location-based services at any time by editing your device settings.You may opt out of receiving push notifications by turning off push notifications at the device level.We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will also retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.Your California Privacy RightsCalifornia Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to echl@echlcom or write us at CA Privacy Rights, ECHL, 116 Village Blvd. Ste 230, Princeton, NJ 08540.Some web browsers may transmit “do-not-track” signals to the websites with which the user communicates. Because there currently is no industry standard concerning what, if anything, websites should do when they receive such signals, we currently do not take action in response to these signals.Changes to this Privacy PolicyWe may update this Privacy Policy at any time to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on the Services prior to the change becoming effective. You should periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.International UsersPlease note that the Services are directed towards users who reside in the United States. Our website is hosted in the United States and our data capture servers are hosted in the EU (European Union). The ECHL personnel and some of the third-parties to whom we disclose your information may be located in the United States or the EU. By using the Services, you consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information in and to the United States, pursuant to the laws of the United States. While some of these countries may not offer the same level of privacy protection as your own, we commit to uphold the privacy protections as explained in this Privacy Policy and take appropriate steps to ensure that recipients of your information are bound to duties of confidentiality.Users from the European UnionThis section of the Privacy Policy applies only if you use our website or Services covered by this Privacy Policy from a country that is a Member State of the European Union, (the “EU”), and supplements the information in this Privacy Policy.In addition to collecting and processing your Personal Data via your use of the Services, as described in this Privacy Policy, ECHL will also collect and process your Personal Data when you attend an ECHL Event (as defined below) in the EU. This section of the privacy Policy describes that collecting and processing.ECHLProperties,LLC is the data controller for processing of information defined as personal data under applicable data protection law (“Personal Data”) when you use the Services.When you attend an ECHL-event or ECHL co-hosted event, including ECHL games at anMember Team arena or at a third-partyarena or other ECHL fan events (“ECHL Event”), we may capture your image, voice and/or likeness, including through the use of CCTV cameras and/or when we film or photograph you in a public location at an ECHL Event. You should expect to be filmed or photographed by CCTV and/or by cameras when you are in a public location at an ECHL Event (e.g. as an audience-member in the arenaif you are attending a game). In addition to describing how we capture and use your image, voice, and/or likeness in this Privacy Policy, we may also display signs at any ECHL Event indicating that you may be filmed or photographed.We will use the Personal Data collected at an ECHL Event:to produce, exhibit, advertise or otherwise use your image, voice, or likeness in any and all media now or existing in future as part of ECHL’s commercial, advertising,media and marketing activities; andin the case of images or footage captured on CCTV cameras, to ensure the safety of the venues hosting ECHL Events and of individuals attending ECHL Events.We process Personal Data for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. Our legal basis to process personal data includes processing that is: necessary for the performance of the contract between you and the ECHL; necessary to comply with legal requirements; necessary for our legitimate interests; and based on consent by our customers, which may subsequently be withdrawn at any time (by emailing echl@echl.com) without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal.In some instances, you may be required to provide us with Personal Data for processingin order for us to be able to provide you our Services and for you to use all the features of our website.We use automated decision-making technologies, including profiling, to support our data processing activities. Our automated decision-making capabilities may send triggered messages based on fan data or behavior. These technologies help us provide a better fan experience for you.We may share your Personal Data with any of the entities set out in this Privacy Policy when it is in our legitimate business interests to do so. Each of the third-party partners may use your personal information for their independent commercial purposes without reference to the ECHL.Please also note that broadcasters and other third parties that are unconnected to ECHL may be independently filming or photographing you when you attend an ECHL Event. Although we only give permission to a small group of entities to film or photograph ECHL Events, these entities are separate data controllers in respect of your Personal Data and ECHL is not responsible for how those parties use your Personal Data and for what purposes.When we transfer your Personal Data to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, some of these parties may be located in countries, like the United States, other than your own, whose privacy and data protection laws may not be equivalent to those in your country of residence. When we transfer your personal information to other countries, including the United States, we apply appropriate safeguards, to protect your information and comply with applicable laws.You may be entitled, in accordance with applicable law, to object to or request the restriction of processing of your Personal Data, and to request access to, rectification, of (e.g. if your Personal Data changes or is out of date), erasure of and portability of your own Personal Data in certain circumstances. Requests should be submitted by contacting us by emailingechl@echl.com.If you are aware of changes or inaccuracies in your information, you should inform us of such changes so that our records may be updated or corrected. You may lodge a complaint with your local supervisory authority if you consider that our processing of your Personal Data infringes applicable law.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of the Services, please contact us by email at echl@echl.com (or, if you are a user from the EU, at echl@echl.com) or at the following address:ECHLMedia116 Village Blvd. Ste 230Princeton, NJ 08540Attn: Website Privacy Policy
3C28B153-9335-47C6-8182-EDA512A3BB12
Created with sketchtool.
Star 2 Copy
Created with Sketch.
83849D66-8CC8-47EF-8FF3-576CCFD2EB58
Created with sketchtool.
Artboard
Created with Sketch.
Reading Royals R Logo (1)
Group 106
Created with Sketch.
mavs_circle_logo
Created with Sketch.
K-Wings Color
Created with Sketch.
Fav_icon@1x
Created with Sketch.
Icon / Social / Android@3x
Created with Sketch.
icon-dropdown
Created with Sketch.
Check
74C76A34-6D18-406A-B398-6F0CEC077626
Created with sketchtool.
74C76A34-6D18-406A-B398-6F0CEC077626
74C76A34-6D18-406A-B398-6F0CEC077626
74C76A34-6D18-406A-B398-6F0CEC077626
Created with sketchtool.
Created with Sketch.
ADIRONDACK_THUNDER_primary_logo_REV2018@1x
Created with Sketch.
echllogoeps
Created with Sketch.
Group 18 Copy
Created with Sketch.
53079FE7-D159-40A0-8A83-26281B0D3D33
Created with sketchtool.
976DC860-943B-432F-9E9C-CB9AC395B97F
Created with sketchtool.
172C4F03-2B22-49FE-A880-A4C1985B19F7
Created with sketchtool.
53079FE7-D159-40A0-8A83-26281B0D3D33
Created with sketchtool.
976DC860-943B-432F-9E9C-CB9AC395B97F
Created with sketchtool.
172C4F03-2B22-49FE-A880-A4C1985B19F7
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
0CCDF29C-1F7C-4F46-921A-EC230ACEE372
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
86A6C4DD-D877-4C22-A527-8B9666AA9DD0
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
42E886A7-7224-4FDC-BBEB-01976002C351
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
40C8A19E-A06F-4836-ABD8-C5AE68BC33DB
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
644E21E0-3CB1-4F6B-B321-22391C0CD429
Created with sketchtool.
team-logo / WIN
Created with Sketch.
team-logo / PW
Created with Sketch.
team-logo / LOST
Created with Sketch.
team-logo / PL
Created with Sketch.
0CCDF29C-1F7C-4F46-921A-EC230ACEE372
Created with sketchtool.
033561FA-5AC5-424E-BFCB-752595AE0B20
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
0CCDF29C-1F7C-4F46-921A-EC230ACEE372
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
86A6C4DD-D877-4C22-A527-8B9666AA9DD0
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
53079FE7-D159-40A0-8A83-26281B0D3D33
Created with sketchtool.
976DC860-943B-432F-9E9C-CB9AC395B97F
Created with sketchtool.
172C4F03-2B22-49FE-A880-A4C1985B19F7
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
86A6C4DD-D877-4C22-A527-8B9666AA9DD0
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
42E886A7-7224-4FDC-BBEB-01976002C351
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
40C8A19E-A06F-4836-ABD8-C5AE68BC33DB
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
644E21E0-3CB1-4F6B-B321-22391C0CD429
Created with sketchtool.
033561FA-5AC5-424E-BFCB-752595AE0B20
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
40C8A19E-A06F-4836-ABD8-C5AE68BC33DB
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
644E21E0-3CB1-4F6B-B321-22391C0CD429
Created with sketchtool.
7CB4E955-9512-49F4-B03B-933CF03CA2FD
Created with sketchtool.
53079FE7-D159-40A0-8A83-26281B0D3D33
Created with sketchtool.
976DC860-943B-432F-9E9C-CB9AC395B97F
Created with sketchtool.
172C4F03-2B22-49FE-A880-A4C1985B19F7
Created with sketchtool.
45E49ECC-5769-44F4-97EA-EDE23E5CB428
Created with sketchtool.
CC731668-0119-48B2-B401-BACA731EA471
Created with sketchtool.
0CCDF29C-1F7C-4F46-921A-EC230ACEE372
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
86A6C4DD-D877-4C22-A527-8B9666AA9DD0
Created with sketchtool.
9EE80E93-DA55-44A3-BB86-719DDC115D67
Created with sketchtool.
42E886A7-7224-4FDC-BBEB-01976002C351
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
C38CE427-9814-4B47-91C9-66896A6EB2BE
Created with sketchtool.
40C8A19E-A06F-4836-ABD8-C5AE68BC33DB
Created with sketchtool.
763B01E1-3D00-402A-B0C3-1DD729BBA531
Created with sketchtool.
644E21E0-3CB1-4F6B-B321-22391C0CD429
Created with sketchtool.
033561FA-5AC5-424E-BFCB-752595AE0B20
Created with sketchtool.
033561FA-5AC5-424E-BFCB-752595AE0B20
Created with sketchtool.
Icons/Search/1000
F3916FC0-768E-4027-A1D5-CC66110459CF
Created with sketchtool.
Created with sketchtool.
Icons/Attachment/1000
Created with Sketch.
CB_Linked_Icon_Arrow
